[Music]
hello and welcome to the junkyard love
podcast
[Music]
at what age do we learn how to have
better conversations
at what age do we learn to have better
conversations with ourselves
what's brack in my bros welcome to the
junkyard love podcast i'm pumped you're
here it's me your host
the guy from the outside of the pringles
cans today the recommendation that i'm
going to give you
is in the form of an app that i use i
don't get paid for this
i'm not sponsored by this anything it's
just something that has helped me
personally in my life
it's helped me change my conscious
reality it's helped me
be a better man help me be a better
person it's helped me understand my
confusing at times mind
the recommendation is the waking up app
by sam harris they have a 28-day
meditation course
uh to get you into a meditation habit
this is i think probably the biggest
factor that has gotten me into a daily
meditation habit the last couple years
um there's a lot of theory there's a lot
of conversations with different
types of zen teachers or different types
of meditation teachers
it's very it's very down-to-earth in an
intense way it's quite wonderful they
have
um different types of meditations they
have just so many things that you can
put in your headphones it's great to
start your day with
a lot of the times we don't really
understand meditation we're like what am
i doing following my breath i think i'm
pulling my breath i don't know how to do
this
it's confusing what this app will do is
it teaches you what's going on
it explains things that are right in
front of your eye that you didn't think
that were actually happening
um the app is paid there's a free
version the app's paid but all you have
to do if you want if you want the app
send sam harris email just send them a
support email and say hey i'm not making
a ton of money right now
uh whatever it is no questions asked
they will give you the whole app for
free that's what i did no shame in my
game i was like hey i can't afford it
right now i'm not gonna pay extra for
this app
but i really love it i've listened to
every second of this app
it's changed my life it's just it's
quite fantastic
and i highly recommend it to anyone
learn about your mind
learn about your emotions learn about
your reality
check it out waking up app from sam
harris let's get rolling the podcast
it's me it's jazzy it's trev we have
just the most wonderful conversation
ever it's great i loved it
i had such a good time i'm really
excited for you guys to hear so take
care of yourselves
if you're furling your brow at the
current moment
let go let go of the tension in your
shoulders if you haven't drank any water
get a cup of water pause this right now
get a cup of water drink some water
stretch do your thing love yourself
let's go
everybody's like so jumbled around and
there's going to be this like all right
are we trying to
get last year back or are we trying to
get cap caught back
up with this year like this all just a
conundrum though and
it's crazy that the government had a
bunch of money
saved up for people like and we never
would have thought that
like they just had a bunch of money on
the side that they could give stimulus
checks out for and stuff you know which
is kind of crazy
yeah or do they like they're totally
gonna buy this they're like i don't know
hopefully we figure out where that money
could come from later thank you from our
taxes next year
yeah yeah they just slowly bend us over
the next day
yeah dude it's just weird i mean it's
been so difficult to think of like
like because day by day my thoughts
change on the whole thing yeah like you
know the last month i'd say i do
like it doesn't affect me like
anxiety-wise as much but like the first
couple months
the first month month and a half i was
like bro i'm not leaving the house i'm
like i'm not even getting anywhere near
amazon packages
i don't like and i kept just like
feeding my brain like i was like i need
to know what's really going on
so i'm trying to like listen to
neuroscientists trying to listen to
biologists i'm trying to listen to like
all these intelligent people
and they're terrified so i'm terrified
too they said uh
bill gates retired to make the vaccine
like oh much conspiracy is saying that
there's so many conspiracies when it
comes to bill gates
what was it is he did they blame him for
the 5g towers
i heard that i heard somebody yeah yeah
that's the thing about conspiracy
theories nowadays you're like i don't
even know i don't know it might be true
might as well give you a good chance and
don't believe facebook
yeah oh man yeah facebook is not where
we got to get our news i go down
youtube rabbit holes of conspiracy
videos what uh what's your favorite
youtube rabbit hole
uh for conspiracies
uh you know build a bird sunglasses i'm
like dude
he's such a turd he's chewing on your
shades
yeah he's like what those weren't mine
probably just like the bilderberg groups
and you know like one world governments
and stuff like that
yeah you know stuff that just
brainwashes your brain
yeah what about you jess what's your
youtube polls illuminati
yeah yeah i get sucked into those okay
so
yeah okay this was legitimately
when i first started like i feel like
because i got kind of into some of those
rabbit holes too a couple years back
and i could i was like what is
illuminati like i was like if someone
would have asked me like
who has never heard of even that word
they'd be like what is that i feel like
i couldn't [__] explain it to him
okay i see like even now i
like i can't explain it but it's scary
like it could be like a really rich
like old white club like where they just
play golf
and stuff or it could be like these guys
really
or jay-z and kanye or the kings and
beyonce's their queen
of black people they're not like they're
not
like dude i don't know like because i
because there's a couple documentaries
even on netflix and stuff like youtube
rabbit holes you could definitely get
some crazy ass documentaries like any
just random person in their basement
could just
alex yeah he has a lot of
rabbit holes yeah but like i don't know
i mean so basically is it like there is
like a secret society running our
society like they're calling the shots
right is that kind of
that's yeah there's like all these like
little
connections like little easter eggs
music videos
yeah and there's like all these i mean
it's hard to
it's it's hard and it's also not hard to
defeat the evidence you're like well i
could see how that's just
a connection you're drawing but i could
also see how that's [__] real i think
it's like the do you believe like
extraterrestrials been here and gave us
tools and all that
um yes you do yeah okay i don't know how
fern sternly honestly at this point but
i think so
i think so too and i think like people
that you can't give the
the public everything that kind of thing
because you might freak
everybody out as in people literally
might start like killing themselves over
yeah
knowing too much information like
there's yeah there's aliens here
and you know they're like in the white
house
you know and stuff like that would freak
people out you know
so like do you think it's a good thing
to keep information away from people or
i don't know well so because i was
thinking
okay i feel like they would have to
slowly trickle it into us is the thing
like they would like if they did come
across
like what if 20 years ago like there was
just total contact
with aliens like in and they're like
well we can't just like
post a video on the white house like
twitter and say like hey look at this
alien he's in the white house he's
[__] crazy like my ass off like yeah
but yeah because like but what do you
think would happen i think trevor's
right i think that people would go crazy
like people who are you know uh you know
like let's say
you know very old-fashioned they like
don't really like get it you know people
who have like oh
i'm trying to say older people without
being insulting i'm not trying to sound
as no no
that sounds but like people who don't
challenge their own beliefs too much
they're
pretty stern with what they believe um i
feel like those people would like
like their their reality would they
almost just deny it they'd be like oh
that's
the stuff really they would turn off the
tv and just completely turn them back to
it
and then if they did figure out was real
they might freak out you know
but i don't know man it's a
it's just it's a slippery slope i think
um
there has been a lot like more stuff
that comes out and
things like youtube has helped i think
open people's minds
too maybe this is possible you know not
like
watching the tv ghost hunters or not
that's like kind of like
fake i feel like you know but um
there's a lot of crazy [__] out there i
love going down a good youtube rap the
whole day
i i love it like he loves youtube i
don't watch it as much
you know not too many it's funny i feel
like there's like a whole group of like
that has just slowly stopped watching a
ton of tv
and you just watch more and more youtube
like shaylee will be upstairs watching
tv and i'll come down here and just like
watch youtube on my phone as i just
talked about
he's youtube i'm reality tv she's
watching
reality tv is the key like tonight's
tuesday i watched yesterday
i'm pretty sure like oh okay okay
it's like that yeah it's just funny
stuff like it's good stuff that's a lot
of people are characters like the older
i've gotten i've gotten a lot more like
introvert
too yeah yeah yeah like
i'm just i have like a close knit of
friends i talk to maybe like three or
four people
and like
i feel like i feel like you've always
seemed like an extrovert though yeah
yeah yeah
so we're like yang kind of perfect yeah
yeah
yeah that balance i mean i've definitely
i've always been an introvert i've just
been very my extrovert function which is
very sharp i was just very very good at
it because when i was like
15 16 when i had to start working it's
like dude you got to start
like you got to learn how everybody
works around you because you got to sell
some stuff you got to be good at this
job so
customer service and stuff so um but now
i'm definitely like
very sunken into my like true
introvertness when you worked at the
mr form mr formal yeah i worked at mr
formal
pacsun and munition
yeah and those were all like you know
like one one
i'm working the first half of the day
i'm working and calling people bro
and i'm saying what's up my dude and i'm
gripping their boards and then i go
change and put a shirt and tie on and
i'm like hello ma'am congratulations on
your son's wedding
like you know like you just a bunch of
split different personalities yeah but
it but it sharpened me it really you
know it got me good at people got me
good to
like i learned how to communicate a lot
better with all ages
yeah all ages all different types of
people i mean and now it's
like it's a great skill to have like i
i was kind of forced into it like
there's like like oh i had to get a job
i had to work i was on my own there's
that story
but now as i like revisit it more i'm
like dude those gave me such valuable
skills to like
have to have those hardships to like
force yourself to learn
communication people skills and stuff
but yeah now i'm totally more of an
introvert i definitely
would rather hang out with youtube yeah
freaking
um yeah dude i've had so many bad
jobs and then i was in the weed industry
for three years and that was pretty dope
and um but yeah
freaking you just
always wanted to get to the next thing
though i don't know like i'm trying to
figure out what the next thing
is now that i've been laid off for how
long we've been pandemic
since march since is it like five is it
six months now is it five months
march six
yeah that's so weird that's crazy well
so that's been the thing like
how have you guys i was telling jazz
like it's been difficult to not like
have just like that shame feeling for me
like just because it's just like bro
like i want to be pulling them like
because you can't like
yeah all right i need to go work because
there's just so many limited jobs like
like my industry is just obviously not
down like i gotta totally pivot
yeah um but it's just like i always try
to
to remind myself now it's like dude like
don't like you're not responsible for
the pandemic
like you're just dealing with it yeah
everybody everybody's going through it
yeah because
i've gotten really depressed over it
yeah yeah i even got like
i got i was in the weed industry for
three years i got laid off in
february and um i got clean off like
weed for three months three and a half
months
and then like i wanted to get into this
other job it was like scaffolding and
stuff
and like totally wasn't for me and
really like yeah restart again what am i
gonna do
yeah and and i have tons of photos
unemployment is still nice like i've
saved money
it's been a blessing honestly i've saved
money from the unemployment
but it's still like i feel like a piece
of [__]
i'm not doing anything you know right i
get that man yeah like
it dude it's just this weird ass time
like it's i feel like so many people
feel like that so many people feel like
weird shames from like
not being able to do anything but we're
kind of sitting on our hands like even
people with restaurants and [__] are
like i want to open i want to like work
but we can't open you know and
that's another like you said with your
hands like i i don't want no handout
you know but it's like how am i gonna i
have a kid
you know yeah well that's good though
that you guys are like
you guys have been together so long so
you're able to communicate well and it
seems so you're able to like work out
right now like jazz you're able to
kind of be the breadwinner right yeah
you know that's how i got with shaylee
and i like she's just
totally supporting my house right now
yeah and it's like there is some shame
around it there's like guilt around it
that's that i'll like address
and you know work with through her and
when we talk about but
at the end of the day it's like dude
don't make yourself feel that right and
it's like
we're partners so like obviously if
there was a time where i
couldn't work he would do it like yeah
help each other out lean on each other
we also took in two other kids
tell me about this yeah we took in
my best friend tesla we took in her two
kids
which her three-year-old is 18 days
older than my desmond and then her
daughter is a year old and we had them
for eight
weeks right at the
[Music]
you have to have more money if you want
like more than one kid yeah
yeah yeah that's of course and even with
one kid you gotta have one we do not
want twins ever
yeah yeah that was experience so two
three-year-olds and a one-year-old
for eight weeks or you're saying like
the like dez and the other one were like
twins together
18 days apart yeah yeah yeah and
the same personality trace they're
picking up literally yeah yeah
and they were off the wall off the wall
so
and the one-year-old tyler tyler she was
one
the best one at all but she was she was
fine but hopefully other ones don't hear
this
yeah no no they've altered four
next month they're just starting
podcasting at age four yeah yeah
but yeah that was crazy and then it was
a pandemic so we couldn't go anywhere i
couldn't take them
to a park or to the zoo so i literally
we were in the house
just trying to unless it was me going to
the grocery store
being with them and i had to be a
teacher to all three
and a mom basically to all three like
y'all are beasts that's awesome 2020
has been i don't think it'll be in vain
but it's been [__] up so far yeah it's
been pretty fun
yeah literally from kobe
to the pandemic into
george floyd too yeah you know it's just
like one thing after another
yeah and um but i think we'll look back
and be like we needed that maybe it was
like a wake-up call
yeah of some sort for real you know i
mean it's it's weird
it's strange like i forgot i'm not a
sports fan so it hasn't been like the
forefront of my mind but it's strange
and i kind of forgot about kobe like i
don't think i've thought about that in a
couple weeks but that's like whoa
that was the first thing yeah i wasn't
like huge into like superheroes growing
up but like
guys like kobe or lebron or whoever
yeah yeah like skateboarders in the same
sense exactly exactly no i look
i dude i played all the tony hawk
underground one
two and three yeah like the music for
this tony hawk's games are always dope
for kids the soundtracks front to back
are good like you could still pull them
up now when you're out on the boat and
yeah this is made for it yeah
exactly and uh even though like they
came out with skate and that was like a
lot more realistic
yeah i like skate better i like skate i
played one and two
i i don't know i think people that do x
games those guys are
insane dude like
you gotta have so much balls to do that
[__] bro go down those
[__] fat
ramps ramps yeah then they jump out and
[__] yeah dude like
bro that is crazy like like i feel like
sports extreme sports all of these like
we just keep humans are so badass yeah
like i was listening to this podcast
about
these dudes yeah dude like these dudes
who uh
they surf big waves and it's like if
they don't just surf the big waves like
paddling out there they literally get
towed as fast as they can by a jet ski
and it's like
like they don't they're a completely
separate thing than regular surfers now
it's like no we're big wave surfers
that's a whole different
sport i guess and they just like keep
pushing the edge
of extreme sports like uh skateboarding
they just keep getting better and better
they
they find ways to like add more flips
yes and find ways to get more technical
like freaking nigel houston was
like it is so good i watched a little
mini dock on him and
his story's amazing yeah so so you know
his story jazz you know his story
dude okay do you remember who nigel
houston so he used to be on element he
had the super long dreads like down like
you might have like seen him like he's
like a little kid throwing himself down
sets of stairs with like huge dreads or
something or no no no they're uh
rastas kind of family yeah
yeah i don't remember exactly okay but
yeah his story is amazing uh
i guess his dad was like super stern on
him and like
got him to be a pro and like
basically installed all the fundamentals
and stuff
right and then um his mom
went to cali with his two brothers and
they're like split up and so at this one
arizona tournament they like
made he wanted to go with his mom so
like he set it up to where he got to
leave with his mom like after that
tournament or something i don't know but
and be like a regular kid in cali and
he cut his dress and he's like all inked
up now and
yeah dude he's live on instagram yeah
he's flexes on instagram man he's just
covered in
audis and hot [__] all day
from his story trev was uh that his like
dad was like would keep him from school
like you can't go to school today you
need to [__] escape you're gonna be a
skater yeah yeah like
we like trained him like a little
skateboard he would take his money that
he
his winnings and like went and bought
like a huge farm
in like puerto rico or something like
that oh he took his money too i didn't
know he took his money i didn't remember
that
it was crazy it sucks all right but what
do you think if you are the best like
he's debatably one of them
like like what like how do you think
niger feels today like probably
conflicted different days
but he's probably like you know like
look at this life i have around me if i
didn't work as hard as i did
pretty much yeah but i think he does
give him the respect for that
yeah i just don't see him like like in
his pictures or anything though i don't
know
yeah i think he still lives over there
or something but yeah nigel houston's
like the best
i was watching this show um i don't know
it's like that it's on amazon prime
and it's called the boys it's basically
like um like bad superheroes
and uh spoiler if anybody's listening to
this but
they basically find out that like the
superheroes who were like saving the
world and stuff they were actually like
their parents gave them this injection
like you could basically go to a company
and like all right your kid's gonna be a
superhero like they're set for life
but they've got to save the world when
they're older whatever it is it's like
it's almost like a like damn i'm a
superhero like that's the best thing but
then it's like wait i didn't have a
choice though
yeah i think it's kind of like this he's
like he's like i'm a superhero of
extreme sports like
you know skateboarding i'm good at it
but i didn't really have a choice yeah i
was kind of brainwashed into i guess he
could stop
and then um you remember the movie lords
of dog town yes
like they were like the og's of the area
you know they kind of started
i always thought that was like a good
movie dude i love that movie yeah
that was so i i really like that because
it shows like
like how technical the all these sports
like they like
they just get so technical so fast like
one person does something
in front of someone else and it gives
them permission like oh you could do
that i never thought to try that
like like are you a skateboarder yeah
yeah i grew up in a skateboard
for a while but i can't skateboard
really well but i can long board
and i i would go to the skate park with
j lap and adrian ty
and just sit there sometimes you could
skate
but you know i'd go to the skate parks
too
yeah yeah it's just like you've probably
been at skate park when i was at the
skate park
probably you were one of the skatepark
chicks
oh my gosh smoking a few packs over in
the corner yes maybe some marbs
yeah back in my cigarette days that's
funny he hasn't smoked since dez
oh really yeah going right over yours
hell yeah
or what was that like was that difficult
or was it just like a decision
like i got pregnant i said i'm not
smoking and then like after i had dez
the smell i didn't want nothing to do
with it oh
i just can't be around it anymore and i
smoked for like 10 years
yeah yeah it was bad that's so cool i
feel like that has something to say
about like
you know like i have a on the wall over
there you give things power
yeah i've talked about that before like
you like dude there's things in our
brain when you're like no
yeah i'm not doing it like and then like
later like your biology will catch up
with you it's like all right that smells
like [__] now
yeah i don't know i don't have an
addictive personality yeah
that's awesome trevor does i don't
does your parents have any addictive
yeah yeah members
yeah my dad um my dad got into meth
pretty hardcore when i was like nine
okay
um and then i don't my mom doesn't
really have any addictive personalities
when it comes to
like drugs or alcohol or anything i
don't think yeah
and my dad's he's good now he's smoke
some pot now but
but he's good now um yeah and we were
talking about addictive addictive
personalities
it's like i don't know i i didn't think
that i really like had much of addictive
personality like i was always really
good at like
um like once in a while you know you
have a couple too many and you notice
you're like okay i shouldn't have went
past that beer whatever but for the most
part it was like i can control that [__]
i control it like
but what i was telling you guys earlier
when it comes to like
extremities sometimes i'll just i have
to go all in like it's i can't just run
i'm saying i can't just run a mile i
gotta run like seven miles yeah like
yeah
just going all in and like having to be
obsessed with something like pushing it
to the limit
yeah and i i don't know i mean i think
that kind of like
that's kind of like how you can
sometimes control your addictive
personalities in a way like shove it
like filter it into something that's
good for it like you know it's not so
bad to run all that or it's not so bad
to go work out for a certain amount of
time or
like whatever or like if you're all
in and just like obsessed with watching
tutorials or or something that's
beating your brain but yeah um
does your parents have any addiction
yeah so um
i don't really know my dad we just like
met when i turned 18
but my mom my mom and my stepdad got
into drugs
when i was 13 when reynolds it was the
red
warehouse aluminum foil right right when
they closed down
they got into drugs so my mom
she probably doses still into it off and
on but i don't think she does because i
can notice when she's on it when she's
not on it right right
but my stepdad's still on it which is
treasures dad
and then um i never got into it like
it just wasn't for me i didn't want to
do drugs
i i would say i got like i wasn't like
uh addicted to alcohol but i was like
the party
right right the uh get to the party
around people yeah like if if it was if
they were doing it i would do it
right right yeah we can leave it
then no more after tonight yeah kind of
thing yeah right yeah
yeah it's it's interesting you know i
like
it's not just our town like it's so many
other small towns
everywhere like alcohol and like you
know
all these things like it's just weird
that you know however many years ago
what
60 years ago like this wasn't such a
normal thing like not every single
person was drinking not every single
person was
like dabbling in weird drugs or yeah i
mean i think that everybody should
experiment with
with what they feel comfortable with
yeah and if they can control it you know
it's your own consciousness but
it sucks how many how much we don't know
about a lot of it and so it catches
people off guard like oh
definitely with my dad i know that he
began it originally for
pain he had full bone arthritis and like
the medications they were giving the
doctor wasn't working
you know and it's and i'm not justifying
what he did by any means it sucks
but it's like there's so many stories
like that if you just listen to anybody
who's like really had it bad like a lot
of times they have
some defining reason of of how it got
them started anyway like after that you
know it becomes their own justifications
and
as addicts we feed into our own [__]
a lot yeah
you know that initial like like man why
why'd you like have to go down that
what's up with that why
what was the need you were trying to
fill because you could get it somewhere
else you know
so see with me my mom did
uh heroin and meth and you know growing
up i was like
why do you love that why do you love
that more than your kids you know
what is causing this so i tried it
yeah and i could tell yeah it's cool
it's a
out of this world type of high right but
it wasn't for me
i knew i don't want to be like my mom
i'll never be like my mom
right so i just never stuck with yeah it
didn't like hook you a lot of people a
lot of times people say like
like that i knew in my head i was like
okay i can see why she likes it so much
oh so it kind of helped you emphasize it
it did a little bit
this will transition perfect into how
desmond saved me i think
yeah yeah um he did
my parents were like very like i grew up
in like a domestic
violence drug house a bunch of different
houses growing up
and um and then like my mom and dad
divorced when i was like six or seven
and then she would have like all these
like boyfriends that would
get clean for like eight months they'd
go to n a and stuff and then next day
they would relapse and stuff like that
and um my house definitely was like my
mom
enabled the [__] out of me growing up
like i housed the party house
like we could do whatever and
go wherever come back whatever you know
and then
after high school i got to the point to
where like
i got really into so i smoked
i started smoking weed like 14 15 you
know
and um that turned into
[Music]
i turned into doing like going to party
like i always told garrett mccoy this
like him and brittany lee like corrupted
me because they started bringing me to
like parties and stuff you know because
you were younger
and um i was doing like a bunch of party
drugs you know
ecstasy coke drinking whatever
and then that turned into i got into
pain pills a little bit and um
wasn't because you broke your foot or
ankles yeah i did i did break but i
found the picture of that the other day
i have a picture of me in my boot and i
like pretty much
almost they said it would have been
better if i would have broke my ankle
but it was like pretty much broken i
guess
and um started doing uh
prescription pills and that turned into
like
snorting them smoking um and then
trying to get that more high yeah and
then it got super expensive
on the street by the time i graduated
and then
um it was like i can't buy these anymore
and that that led me to heroin
and i'm with jazz so people think like
why are you that like sad or why are you
that upset to get to that point when you
have like a really good girlfriend
and like uh like a pretty good family
that supports you
you know for them for the most part but
like
uh like i was just so enabled growing up
you know from [__] and so like that led
me to heroin
i was 21 and then
she was seven months pregnant and i did
it for like
like seven eight months not you know
and so like i decided i want to go to
treatment by myself
which a lot of people don't like it's
more like they go to jail and they want
less jail time or something yeah
and so um or me pushing him but he
wanted to go
yeah for him i only stayed like 30 days
and left
and because jasmine was pregnant and and
then right after desmond was born like
i've never looked back so i got like
four or five years off bad like but hard
drugs
right yeah well good for you bro that's
awesome yeah that's pretty much
my story that's well dude seriously and
i played sports and stuff in high school
and i was doing like [__] during games
too
right right right like so you don't feel
anything yeah get that extra
football player you weren't alone at all
yeah
is a weird place dude yeah yeah
people are just doing [__] you know all
the time like
it's just so easy to get into i feel
like almost as a
teenager here i don't know maybe not for
no sadly it is
no i think it is kids that grew up here
that like
have or maybe more warsaw because they
have money you know to spend
yeah well that's the thing i mean like
even rich kids have their problems like
a lot
i knew a lot of rich kids who like once
i got to know them or i'd be to their
house a couple of times like i'd be like
oh okay so like your parents are having
like you're having a rough time at home
too like your parents are arguing your
parents are drinking your parents
they're having
their own prescription drugs like dude
it's like everybody just kind of has
their [__]
it just doesn't seem like we have a way
to know how to deal with it and so we
just try to like kind of be comfortable
you know recovery
yeah like having such a crazy life
growing up like
i would never want to deal with my
feelings like
i thought i could just do some [__] some
some kind of dress like and then when i
finally went to treatment
dealt with the feelings like head-on
like that [__] was
i needed that i needed to feel that yeah
sometimes you got to feel those feelings
yeah you do man you got because they're
there to teach you you got to sit with
them a lot of times we're like we see
them and we're like oh get away from
that and you're trying to get away from
it but
sometimes just sitting with it will help
you understand it did you what did you
is there anything that like you can
bring up now that you remember that
stuck out a lot from treatment like you
were there you know 30 days it's like a
good amount of time you know that's
did you learn a lot there or
it's the old indian ritual where they do
the feather and the smoke
uh what's it called oh know that one i
can't remember what it's called
smudging smudging yeah and we did that
we wrote our whole life stories and then
we threw it in the fire
and then we'd smudged how did that feel
yeah
did you feel it from like throwing in
the fire yeah
there's some people like crying and
stuff you know it's like a
being baptized or something you know
kind of yeah and so
uh i liked it it was dope
um the thing that the treatment i went
to was like
um the schedules was really bad like
you had too much time to sit i feel like
like you'd go like to like you'd wake up
really early go to breakfast then you
would
um you'd have like a class and then
you'd have like a two hour wait
in between so you literally just be like
sitting in your room doing
like homework or like i don't know it
just got like really
too spaced out i feel like your day
wasn't filled enough
but there's like different one like are
are all like
rehab centers different like yeah like
it's just they have different activities
everyone's different everyone's
different um the one i went to was in
tootle and then there's like one in like
vancouver
what's crazy is i was in detox for five
days
and then um i was in detox for five days
and then i
they didn't have a room for me there and
i had to get sent back to town
and i was literally back in town for
like 20 days before i go to bed
and so i was like [__] but yeah it's not
crazy that you have to wait for beds and
[__]
i always i remember hearing that term
like oh there's no beds open so i can't
get clean
yeah [__] that's [__] up yeah and then
like and then they'll get dirty
until they have a bed yeah dude because
they're just trying to like
like hold out to the next one because
right because you can't like a lot of
times you get so
like these places where you can't
actually get clean by yourself because
these are
be so sick so [__] exactly people die
from withdrawals and [__]
yeah like ah damn dude okay so
so you you benefited from the the
writing a life story and
throwing it in there that's pretty cool
there's um yeah and then like uh
there's just like some dope ass
counselors that's usually yeah
there's usually like one or two you can
find they can just talk to
and um just being around people that's
going through the same [__]
and uh you know like having meetings and
stuff but like
at the end of the day you know you're
leaving and you got to come back to the
town and stuff so like
in real life in real life and so like
you know that at least i knew that so
like
but i was four or five years ago and
yeah
totally different guy now yeah a long
time ago it's
so different like you you have no idea
but
um
[Music]
my mom i've taken her to treatment like
three or four times too so like
in the back of my head too i was always
like i'm not going a million times like
her
and having a kid on the way like
it's not gonna happen um my mom's doing
really good now though
i should say that she's two and a half
years clean
yeah good awesome good for her hell yeah
it's been a rough
yeah jasmine's had issues with her
like yeah over the years oh [__] oh yeah
well you gotta do what you gotta do [__]
it's such a weird position to be in
that's my mom and your girl you know
no doubt man life is a lot more
complicated than they make you believe
puzzle pc man that's tough um but
yeah it's gotten a lot better she's like
our number one babysitter
now yeah um she probably loves that
she does i think loki he that's what
saved her life too
she says that i know yeah so so how
what were your thoughts like like when
it was finally do you think it was just
like
one day you're just like [__] all right
like we got a baby on the way like it's
time i gotta do this like was there a
breaking point was that
it was that definitely the car wreck i
got a car wreck
i total my acura i had well and i was in
the car pressure
and he was on drugs and so
that and um
yeah so that's a huge way to do stupid
[__] when you're doing drugs dude
yeah it's so easy to be like a bad
person i tell this to people all the
time it's so easy to be a bad person
it takes work to be a good person mm-hmm
it actually does
hate is easy love is hard
uh you know like
i just have so many like cool jerseys
and [__]
and that you sold yeah and all that [__]
dude
and i was just like for some stupid [__]
you know so
all that accumulated to getting clean i
think
but thank god i'm like young i got my
dad he's like
not doing too hot right now he's in his
50s he's going to be 50
we don't want to be 50 year old still on
the streets like
come on y'all no yeah you got to start
working now and it'll add up
yeah and you just want like a new
generation to
just for dads to be there and for
normal [__] to go on at least like in
the house
you know and i feel like a lot of
families don't have that
yeah so okay well so shaylee and i are
still like we're
we're generally like still we have days
where we're like undecided we're like we
don't we don't actually don't know if we
want to have kids but we do
we also have days where we're like we
think we we will like we're up and down
we haven't like
talked to me four years ago yeah like
how dare you bring a child into this
crazy world
right right well okay so so if you did
have to like
um so just what what have you guys
learned like
personally from life like what is what
are things that like you want to make
sure you instill and dez
like what are things that or even things
that maybe at the beginning you didn't
think you would want to teach them but
now you're like oh this is definitely
important like what
well these kids don't just grow braces
that too
yeah you're taught racism for sure
and so like but like uh
even me i'm i didn't have death tolls 27
so i want to show dez that he doesn't
need to be a little preteen having kids
like most of the world
these days my cousin had a kid i didn't
i didn't i was like you guys i didn't
want kids
i thought oh i'm never having kids like
out of all my friend groups that i have
everybody has kids getting married yeah
never
want to bad luck get married
now he wants to get married yeah dude
yeah you don't know what you don't know
you don't know it's so beautiful like
when you can look back and see how much
you change you're like oh man i was so
full in
[__] myself i love changing i love you
now we love that we have a good kid
yeah oh yeah dude for the world
so what is what is having a kid taught
you guys
patience 100 you have to have patience
yeah when they're screaming mama mama
mama
oh 50 times in a minute it's like no
dude i hear you dude
i'm right here freaking uh
desi he's bossy too yeah he's super cool
he's like
my chin over
[Laughter]
when i'm trying to edit photos like no
uh-uh
[Music]
patience for sure and um
oh just obviously like like he's
your biggest responsibility you know
yeah
it's the number one thing and um
responsibility 100
because i was well kind of still am but
i love to party
yeah i love all that
planning
[Applause]
yeah uh
dez was two and we went to kendrick
lamar
concert and we took ecstasy or acid yeah
and we made sure we didn't see him the
next day because it's still in your body
and we didn't want to touch it
yeah right so we planned it out yeah
yeah dude yeah
explore your consciousness learn about
[__]
uh wally was last october i would love
to see what he did acid there
he came to the crowd and hugged us
hugged us
high-fived us yeah it was awesome
and we were rolling yeah yeah so like
you know
that was awesome but it's like a once
every year and a half
right one is planned out make sure like
you said even the next day like yeah i
do i know i know
um you know parents who still do the
same thing like they do the same thing
and yeah
they've definitely matured in so many
ways like totally i guess they're kind
of like hippie parents
dude i don't know i mean i think just
down to earth
parents like a lot of yeah down the
earth yeah there's a lot of stuff i feel
like when we were growing up there's a
lot of well
i guess we we three actually had
peculiarized we knew about drugs at
young ages but very young outside of
that it's kind of like this like don't
even talk about it like i know more
conservative like friends who like
um you know like they weren't around
drugs because their parents weren't
doing drugs and so it's almost like this
like you don't even talk about it
so you don't know anything about it but
i feel like when we can
learn about it and you know from
experience like i feel like if dez came
comes to it to an older age and
it's like all right what's this about
and just get the question popped on
i won't be like my mom and i won't do
stuff with him
yeah i'm gonna put a line at that yeah
my first time smoking weed was with my
mom yeah my dad
see yeah so i don't want to do that but
i do want to be
to an extent parent with him that's
still like
when he's like 21 or 18. you know
yeah maybe he's got a graduation or
graduation
night you know let's say yeah yeah
yeah as long as ducks are in a row
exactly right yeah
it's something that he wants to do for
sure learn about it there's so much
information
out there now though that we didn't have
like like we got phones in
2007 or iphone i would say iphone came
out in 2007
and like right around that time was when
you could start like
like google wasn't always a normal thing
where you just hop on whatever you
[__] want to know the world is in
your hand
literally yeah like and if you wanted to
know about weed or any of that stuff
back then you got to go to the dealer's
house and you got to ask him
you got to go to [__] sketchy smoking
house that's true that's that late aunt
yeah dude and you're gonna and someone's
gonna tell you a bunch of stupid stuff
that's not actually real about it but
it's gonna make you excited about it the
first phone you had
was the first phone you had the first
phone i had yeah
uh first phone i had was oh it was
definitely a pay as you go like you
bought the minutes for it
mine was two nokia
10th grade yeah what about you what
grade i was in eighth
or wait well technically sixth grade i
had a
virgin mobile flip phone but i had like
a few bugs on it and i just bought
ringtones
and then i did ring those we always talk
about those like ringtone music wraps
um eighth grade i got like a slide up
samsung but when you were in eighth
grade i was
you know i didn't get a phone until i'm
like my junior year in high school
yeah and that's when myself i'm five
years older than that yeah
middle school yeah my space was
definitely popping off around that all
through
sixth through eighth grade and then
literally right when i got literally
right when i got to
ninth grade it was facebook yeah
dude yeah and that because now we can
pull out our phones at any time and
search whatever we want like with it
it's like an appendage like it's a part
of our bodies you don't leave the house
without it my watch i can look up stuff
yeah it's constantly like consuming it's
gonna be taking your heart rate and all
that stuff everything it already does
but
i mean it's okay so what do you guys
think the algorithms
yeah the algorithms they're brainwashing
us probably we're probably just [__]
robots yeah
but you know everything you want how do
you guys think i feel like
social media and like phones yeah but
like all in that like all that
technology
i feel like it changed our society so
[__] fast man
like it i feel like it transformed us
like
so for good and bad for good as in like
it's helped her business out right my
businesses
yeah for bad so there's kids that
literally want to like kill themselves
over this [__] you know
yeah you get so bad so many self-esteem
issues or just if you take their phone
away
they get so upset well this we're
talking about
the addiction personality yeah we've
made these kids addicts absolutely
like if you look at the like
neurochemical things happening in their
brains it's
things that don't lie about the same
things that an addict has it's crazy i
don't know where my phone's at for a
minute i'm like
okay yeah i mean i'm not saying that i
don't yeah yeah
for sure but uh no the kids definitely
are
off on one on the cell phones and when
we had dez we were like we're not giving
him
a tablet or anything but now it's kind
of like our savior
right right yeah yeah
he likes his tablet do you guys try to
like
like police it at all like try like not
too much netflix anymore
no more netflix he was watching scary
goosebumps and it was giving him
nightmares
he was literally screaming in his sleep
so yeah it's only disney plus or amazon
learning oh there you go yeah yeah
i think you got to put some sort of like
boundaries on it i have
i i know people around my life who like
give their kids the phones and it's like
whatever you want like one time we were
sitting there
and we were talking about we should have
been more aware of him being in the room
but we were talking about like political
stuff is right when the coronavirus was
happening
and then he contributes he starts
talking about um
it's one of my like family members but
he starts talking about like
some article that he's reading like uh
so so and so
president has coronavirus blah blah and
we're like wait what you're a little kid
why are you looking that up
he was like searching it up because he's
trying to contribute to the conversation
that way yeah
but like you got to put you know
boundaries on that yeah
yeah i'm sure it's so difficult though
it is i don't even know how you block
stuff from like google and stuff
i do you do okay youtube yeah
youtube for sure
jazz i want to talk a little bit about
um your work your photography so you've
definitely you've taken pictures for me
multiple times i have we've done events
together
and events yeah
and you've been in the damn game for a
while yeah i feel like
i always just love hearing the
perspective of of the artist of the
person who is
who is behind the lens you know yeah um
so so give me a little bit of your
background like what you've done
um in the photography world and then
maybe just like like what have you
learned and how have you changed your
style and any of that
yeah so when i first started out about
seven years ago when i really got into
it
i was taking them off my iphone like i
would have
clients and take their pictures off my
phone and so now having
now i go to weddings with two cameras
i'm like
ready but uh i just love photography
um i if i could i wouldn't charge
anybody and i would just
do it because that's how much i love it
but of course
she puts her heart and soul it's nice to
be paid to do what i love
um i'm up yesterday or saturday was my
39th wedding and we just did one i was
just in a wedding i got to see her
i got us here in action you got to see
me in
yeah you got to tell people where to go
you're the boss yeah
100 but uh yeah so
i just love photography yeah yeah
yeah couples and newborns and i do yeah
you get like experience
like i feel like you probably definitely
enjoy the experience of like
you gotta live that with them literally
that's like a photographer
or the clients that i have from five
years ago and they stay with me and i
literally
watch their kids grow incredible it's so
awesome like
one year old they were crying the whole
time now they're five look how good he's
smiling for me like
it blows my mind yeah and both studios i
think has helped a lot
bell student yeah so i've worked with
bell students for five years
and they have taught me so much that i'd
even
knew you could do right right with
lights and
different flashes and just everything
and learning the camera
right where the first couple years i
stayed in auto i don't know if you know
what that means
but on the computer i stayed within auto
and
as of now i am full on manual i know
which way to turn it for sun shade where
before i didn't know
none of that i'm all self-taught yep do
you do
photography no no i don't i i
uh i know a little bit just because when
i work in live events
so i know like i mean but if you if i'm
standing next to one of my co-workers i
would say i
know literally nothing just because like
comparatively i know nothing
and jazz i remember she's taking
pictures of you
yeah yeah a good one more than five
probably a couple concerts yeah 360.
yeah you've okay so you've shot for
because we've done
did you do young twist yesterday okay
what about chingy yeah
i did them all oh you did you did yeah
lillard uh
[Music]
that was awesome yeah did you did you
get to meet any of those guys i got
pictures with
all of them yeah was it was there any
okay so i had a way
i'm a [__] i'm a spas especially when
i'm working
yeah i know that i talk really fast and
i'm very likely to do let's go
but like uh i remember yingyang twins
like they got there like
it was right before i was supposed to go
on um
and i remember like they walked in and i
was just trying to like do the work
like just get my job done and so i went
i was like what's up guys great to meet
you
and i basically just was like so here's
what's going to happen i'm going to do
this and i'm going to play this song and
we're going to chant and then you guys
are
going to come out on that are you cool
with that and they're just like staring
at me
and then blankly and they're like bro
you talk too fast and they walked away
from me
oh i was like all right well
let's figure it out they were hella late
too yeah i mean they're always they i
mean they were
they also you know those those string of
years was when
weed had just been legalized over here
so anybody who's flying in from anywhere
is like
i'm going you're taking me to the weed
store before we go to this concert yeah
and i'm buying as much as i can so
every artist that we're doing we're
smoking on the stage
and i'm passing them out yeah for sure
yeah
that's my that's my super exciting yang
twin story but
um yeah you got to meet him and take
photos
yeah they were fun yeah that's so cool i
feel like
when you just when you just like lean
into what you're passionate about you
know it just leads you into areas that
you never thought
yeah oh yeah and it leads you into
learning that you never thought like i
i every day i learned more about audio
then i'm like cool i
i thought i knew i thought i knew this
thing but i don't know [__] about it or
anything
oh recently in the past two months i've
been doing
um photography groups with other
photographers
and we go off and have models and shoot
they they've been teaching me so much
and i'm like i've been in this almost
seven years and i didn't know
any of that just opened my mind and show
me different things to do on my camera
and it just was
awesome well but that's that's the thing
too is is with you is like you're
open-minded and you're
like you're willing to listen to someone
like that like i feel like a lot of
people are like
you know we get too cocky like me when
it comes to djing like i would always go
into things a little too cocky so i'd
miss out on learning experiences
like now i'm not gonna let that go over
my head well there were a few
of the photographers that wouldn't i'd
be like oh this looked a little yellow
do you know what i do and
the girl was literally like oh you just
need to change that and i looked down i
was like
how do i do that what is that and she
walked away
oh yes yeah that's a weird thing and
then the other photographers that i just
went with
all three of them were showing and
introducing everything i'm like
wow these are the ones i needed exactly
yeah those are the ones you want to hang
out with
yeah you we gotta we gotta teach each
other there's so
there's no against anybody like if you
find a cool thing that'll help other
people like shortcut
what tell them right and i feel like why
can like in the photography world
i don't feel like we should all compete
because everybody has their own style
yeah so it's like oh this girl went to
lauren for one time and then they came
to me but then they went to a list and
it's like that's cool cause then they
have all three different sessions
from different eyes different visions
so i feel like there shouldn't be
competition yeah do you ever
do you forget like so
because when it comes to like djing
sometimes it'll be like
just like because if people don't know
anything about djing if they don't know
anything about photography they don't
realize that there's like different
subdivisions it's kind of like hey
will you come play acoustic guitar at my
event i know that you're in a metal band
and you know
you don't want to play acoustic guitar
but you come play right because you do
guitar right
yeah like do you ever get anybody who
like doesn't understand your style or
they
yeah yeah yeah do you do you try to flat
be flexible and like learn that style or
do you have you ever had like turn down
clients where you're like i don't that's
not what i do i've had to turn down
clients
because it's just not my you know not my
area so like um
someone wanted me oh taking pictures in
the rain
oh yeah someone really wanted me to take
pictures in the rain i'm like
i'm sorry my picture's in the rain
there's a raindrop going through your
eye like it's foggy like
i just can't do it right i'm a day
person
i need the light the dryness yeah yeah
yeah yeah i can't take pictures of you
that's probably a whole like
in the photography world that's probably
a whole like difficult thing to do
but there are photographers who can do
it and i'm like
i need to learn from them yeah i i feel
like i notice a lot of
you know like quote unquote styles just
for lack of a more specific word but
there really is
such a vast amount of styles when it
comes to photography
yeah like when you're like you can see
on instagram when you follow certain
pages you can just you can
use mountains and trees and she's more
like people
mm-hmm yeah
yeah everybody edits different yep and
she's even done like
people and lingerie and stuff the door
yeah
they just don't let me put this pretty
open oh yeah i do it all
i mean i was a concert photographer i
never thought in a million years i'd be
taking pictures of concerts and it came
and
i was like yeah and then recently i just
got asked to do
some real estate photos i've never even
thought of that i'm like well sure yeah
yeah i mean i'm sure you can see the
skill set of all the other like little
bits and pieces you've learned
right it might even be a little easier
because there's no objects
moving it's a kitchen
still right so i'm excited to go towards
that
yeah i just want like a variety of
everything in my portfolio
yeah that's the best way to do it dude i
saw this thing yesterday that uh
uh this guy i think it was literally in
his instagram bio
and it was just said building my life
resume i was like oh
that's pretty cool and even if it's just
like in one specific area like
photography or
or djing or whatever it is like you're
always
ev you're always learning you know
you're always like adding new knowledge
on top of knowledge and it'll bring you
to places that you didn't
you didn't even know like so even if
there's like one shoot that was a pain
in the butt and it took you a long time
to learn this dumb thing
well you might like next year get an
opportunity to do that same kind of
shoot but now you know how to do it
right something like that yeah like my
friend the other day she
did a wedding with me and uh she put
like these
sun rays in the corner and i'm like whoa
i had to do that so then she like
sent me a video showing me i'm like wow
now i can put
sun rays in the pictures like it's just
cool sunrise on [__] everything
yeah that's that's a cool thing man i'm
glad that i'm glad that you guys are
self-taught like i'm glad that yeah
we have that's what i watch youtube for
yeah man you start djing
i started djing um let's see
it's been like nine years eight years
ago
um yeah i had so my i started djing
i got the interest like i obviously like
always loving it i would go to a bunch
of shows and super into electronic shows
yes i was at cascade at the gorge
um identity fest 2011. you were actually
going to like
big events too oh yeah i was going to go
oh yeah
yeah well we would go to some some some
warehouse raves and [__] yeah
in portland like that i had a couple
years before all that [__] started
getting shut down where i did get a
couple like
legit warehouse [__] ghetto but
awesome raves
but um and then i so i got the interest
at a cascade
show okay and then i uh ended up meeting
up with kelly st
onge yeah i didn't really know shout out
yeah shout out to cal
she's doing our wedding hell yeah good
good i'm glad i'm glad you guys were
able to get somebody
yeah um and and he basically like kind
of
he we talked about it for a while and we
like bonded over electronic music and
stuff because i hadn't really like met
many people who knew electronic music
outside of like my friends and what i
had shown them already right
2010-13 was amazing yeah that kind of
stuff yeah because we were partying
yeah it was the video so he had me
he had me come over to his house um he
taught me a few things and then at the
end i was like oh i really appreciate it
and he's like you want to take it for a
couple
weeks and he literally let me take his
dj controller i didn't know that yeah
bro he helped me out and so i took it
and started practicing and then
yeah within the next year we were
throwing events so we were talking about
gig sesh earlier
basically remember that one anybody
listening who doesn't know if you're not
from the area
um essentially we would have these giant
raves illegal raves out in the woods
like we would find property um and so
there was other people that were doing
them that weren't me
um for a while and we would just go to
those and those
i mean those ones got bigger than mine
those were like 800 people sometimes i
think
all the cops that rated like there's
cops that rated that whole
function like yeah i don't remember what
one but there was one there's um
j laps day and night i remember that one
um i don't know
there was there was the there was one
that cops
or no because there was one where i got
hospitalized
i got kicked in the face i got knocked
out yeah probably was not that one
yeah i mean so this years and years ago
it was one of
i don't remember exactly where it
doesn't matter but yeah uh
essentially like people came there who
weren't there for the music they weren't
there for the invite like they didn't
know anybody there they heard about it
and they came there for trouble like
they came there because they're gonna
they're gonna fight some queers it's
probably their favorite thing
um no that was a different that was that
wasn't mine but that was somebody else's
we yeah we all went to it though yeah
then you had one out
and toodle one time you and j
rob and yeah yeah yeah a couple of the
boys
i was a photographer yes okay so
so essentially it was like the late like
what was that like five years ago
more than that yeah it's been longer
than that yes yeah it's been a while but
so essentially
what we would do is go out to we'd get
generators we'd get speakers anybody
listening who who
never went to these parties um a lot of
times they tried to i'd try to make them
themed um they were totally dangerous
and illegal and you totally should not
do them
um but it was way back then and we would
bring sound systems
lights projectors we would have six djs
we'd go
you know party throughout the night um
it was it was really really it was a
cool thing like i
like i don't contone the the dangers of
like i don't even you know like
it wasn't a safe thing you know but
it was it was so cool man it was really
cool and it really like
it kind of started like i feel like i
brought people together too
yeah dude there's so many cool pictures
like people would post like throwbacks
and i'm like ah
cool yes and it's
i've always been someone like
like if if you don't have a scene make a
scene
you know like dude oh there's nobody in
your town who who does the edm thing you
can't seem to find anybody who's going
to let you
go in their building [__] them you don't
need a building go outside yeah just
make your own party you know
i won't inspire anybody like if anybody
can take something from that like
throwing things
looked amazing
oh yeah yeah and then trying to
hurriedly
pack everything down
around your dj set yeah those are
incredible times we did
even a couple like um i haven't only
always done illegal ones
i've done so i've done a lot of legal
ones too in a couple venues and stuff
but
uh back in the day before i was doing
legal ones i even remember we did one at
a friend's property that was i think you
guys were there
it was a halloween yeah and we basically
set up like six
pop-up tents and like had tarps and like
we basically just made this indoor
yeah it was so much that was crazy yeah
that was tight everybody's stuck
without these yeah outfits yeah i have
so many pictures of those
when people dress up i think that's so
fun it's just
it's it's something different you know
it's something and it's just like
how cool are you gonna be like come on
just do it like
well it makes you like take off your ego
because like if you're wearing like a
dorky wig it's like
like you could try to look cool but you
just look how you do yeah you're wearing
a dress man you could look
feel as cool as you want but yeah none
of that [__] matters like if you feel
like if you're having fun with your
friends you know
who cares what you look like my favorite
was the one um
it was like not going towards rainier
but the other way
and it was a huge field
you were the dj and we had so much fun i
can't remember
right wait is it like up like past class
tonight yes
yes yes it was someone's birthday or
something yeah that was a random one
it was a random one and we used to do it
at uh
crystal nine men's house yeah yeah yeah
yeah and jc used to go up there
yeah and then you dj that your old house
yep yep yeah dude those were my like
first rdg and that was i was like 16 i
was
so gone so far gone
you know like yeah and that's the thing
like i thought it was so cool because i
was with all these older people like
and they weren't even as messed up as i
was i don't think like they're like
handling their [__] and i was just like
out there
like i'm on another dimension yeah so
like
um yeah it was just cool to like
see where we're all at now yeah man
dude people grow and people change and
like
in in i feel like you just take stuff
less serious like you look back and
you're like
[__] right like it was just that time
was crazy
and of course it had to happen because
now i know what i know yeah you know
like but there was like so many house
parties back then i feel like
is there like i don't even know because
i'm not hanging out yeah do high school
kids house party nowadays
i don't think they do oh
yeah like do they still do that i don't
know
did the homies still partay yeah i mean
that's like you grow up and you start
going to the bars more and
there's like a little barrier of like i
don't want to go to the bars and then
you're like
i don't want to go to house parties and
then you get to the nature where you're
like i don't want to
leave the house at all by myself that's
exactly what happens
that's exactly what happens yeah we all
have our stages
um so i do want to get where we've been
talking for a little bit i do want to
talk
about black lives matter i know you guys
have been very um
involved in the movement um i want to
say
i don't want to say that i'm like
uneducated about it but i
am not super into like news media i
don't follow a ton of the social media
about it
i don't watch tv on i don't watch news
on tv i try to understand it like i said
like i try to listen to like
people that i consider to be
intellectual like you know i listen to
like
scientists about [__] and i'm probably
just saying that so i sound [__]
smarter than i am i don't even know
but but i i i just i don't know a ton
about it so
uh i'm still learning yeah yeah so i
um i just don't want to like incorrectly
say anything like i said
i just don't want to put my foot in my
mouth and act like a fool and not know
that i'm acting like a fool so
totally i think it's just good to have
that barrier i suppose but so
um you we did some
um protesting in town right yeah and you
did that we had some peace
we went to the peaceful ones trevor's
been to one i've been to about
10 now okay tell me about him um so
in town um longview kelso
there's a lot of racism a lot of trump
supporters
and a lot of hate um out of
all of them there's maybe been one
that didn't have the haters across the
street i almost got a fight
yelling at us cussing at us so there's
been opposition
every time every single time and it's
because of facebook
they we try to have these private events
and then someone links it and
all the haters come and it's it's
actually like really sad
um i've been on the side where
we did it over by the juvie and uh
we were all protesting and we we stay as
civil as peaceful as possible
if they're yelling at us we try not to
yell back um
all we're trying to do is just stand up
for what we believe in which anybody can
and if they want to they can too
right yeah but um one of the worst
things i heard
from a woman across was said and
might i say i had tons of colored people
around me
all you monkeys go back where you came
from
and it's like more than half of us are
born in longview kelso
or been raised in longview kelso so like
what do you mean
that's so crazy to like actually like
someone in today's day and age saying
that [__] saying that
it blew my mind i wish i had it on tape
i put my phone in my pocket that [__]
would get cancelled
oh my gosh it blew my mind but uh i've
been to see i went to the seattle
protest by myself
was it when it was the um chop the chop
the chad yeah um it was pretty scary
um it was peaceful the day i went um
but just being in that environment made
it scary
um we were right by the police station
and boards up everywhere and
there was a lot of people protesting
cops didn't come
so i wasn't involved in any of those
where the cops have
came um and i just listened to speeches
of different people's stories
yeah that's what i would see a lot of is
like clips on instagram of people like
if you just take a second to listen to
the person the microphone on their hands
like
they'll explain what they're talking
about exactly and they do
and um so that was nice just to hear
every
different perspectives and stuff and
uh but just being down there i was like
i was by my cell so i was terrified
i don't want to be gassed or arrested or
anything but
i didn't really want to go on the ones
up there no you didn't
but i did i had to see it for myself
yeah
because the news media paints like
either this way or this way yeah
like you don't even know what the middle
like what's
right i want to make my own conclusion
myself can you just give me what's
actually going on
exactly and i wish the media would have
been there that day
everybody was just they were doing they
were drawing the black lives matter on
the road and huge letters like
music playing just everybody just
wanting peace
right and for uh for colored and black
people to be
worthy like white people are you know
what i mean so it's just like
it was eye-opener yeah it was cool to
see
yeah do you think that i mean so it's
clearly
i feel like i had this this thought that
i was thinking a while back ago about
like
so when obama became president it was
like we kind of thought that racism was
gone but what it is it kind of like if
you're looking at a map of the u.s and
kind of like started some tornadoes
where it's like here's the racism still
there's
there's people look at these facebook
groups look at these buggers you know
literally um
and so it kind of like stirred up a lot
of that and it's kind of like
you know which is it's how we heal
you know we point out like with those
are the wounds still like we can't
continue to go that way
yeah um but it's just like
it's so crazy to me that there's still
so much opposition it's so crazy to me
that there's people that would go down
and literally just like yell to
someone's face like because because
it's it's not justified but on social
media like you see how nasty people are
and it's like oh because they're a
keyboard warrior it's because they're
safe
it's because they're not seeing another
human being in front of them who has
emotions and feelings in a family
right and like loved ones and their own
like body and everything
they're not seeing that and so it's like
it's it's almost easier to see like okay
on social media yeah i guess
you're like letting it slip and being
crazy there but right for it to even
spill over into like
all these people are now thinking it's
okay to say that to someone's face
yeah and like not feeling remorse they
think that they're right they think or
they have a chance
their guns out and their hands on their
hips and they're literally like
staring at you in the eye and even
pointing at their guns that they're
going
but they literally pointed at their gun
and then pointed at us
do you think that in their heads jazz
that they're like
are they fighting the they're not
actually like
against you guys in that specifics like
they're not against you in their own
town
they're fighting the narrative of the
rioters
they're fighting yeah like like there is
racism there
there is race involved in that for sure
yeah but i feel like a lot of those
people
they think that like like oh they're
holding a blm sign
so they must represent everything bad
that i've ever seen on the news who is
also
listening so they do yeah and that is
just you think that
there's common reduction in common sense
would would be like oh okay that's not
what these people are doing right when
we're trying to show them that we're not
yeah we're peaceful protesters we're not
the writers we're not the ones that are
taking advantage of this situation and
burning down buildings like
right we don't want to do that no i
don't like that
we're just trying to get our word across
we just want to be heard
yeah when you're being supportive of
people who are fighting in bigger cities
and stuff and you're saying we're with
you too
we're with you too yeah and we're
everywhere and um
even even downtown portland they
none of them want any of that violence
or any of that
but the people are fed up too the
police put men and the government
just fire at us so hard that
what we're supposed to sit back and take
it you know what i mean it's like we've
got to fight back too
yeah i don't know so i'm like on both
sides kind of like i don't want it but
then again i don't want to sit here and
just take it
yeah i mean it's an important time it's
like if it's like if some [__] needs to
change you got to like push it forward
that's for sure like
sometimes you like sometimes you need
the rebellion you know yeah
like i think that when it comes to the
[__] media man
it's just so down in portland there
would be
like at night there was like 50 days in
a row where there was at night time like
the bad riots
and those were like that was where it
was like it wasn't all
it wasn't just blm it was like it was a
bunch of people like
just trying to tear [__] down they're
just angry the people who are just
probably you know scared it's a pandemic
right now a lot of crazy stuff is going
on
and it got mixed up with the blm stuff
but then there'd be
that same night from a different news
station you go down the road and there's
people singing together
right and they're they're they're like
they're together
it's just like speeches and everybody's
sitting crisscross applesauce
yeah it's crazy but it sucks because you
know based off of what algorithm you
follow what data
you have what the data they have on you
you're going to get fed these different
narratives
and then you get to a point where you
know we see with a lot of um
a lot on both sides really is like our
own confirmation biases
like once you can get you know 13 likes
when you post something that's kind of
[__] mean
but you it's the people that are on your
back they're going to give you those
likes now you're like okay
it's cool to say it yeah i can say it
out loud i got these are my people they
support me
and it's like now it's okay to say weird
racist [__] on facebook or something oh
my gosh
no it's not the other day remember i was
i sometimes i can't just keep my mouth
shut i have to say something so i said
something to one of them
and it literally turned into a six hour
argument with all these no
you did not give six hours of your life
to facebook jasmine
damn you just hours and hours
it sucks you in it's very hard to see
arrogance and not be like what i
can explain that out of you i think
right i tried
i dude i used to do it all the time like
i would always i always wanted to be the
um the moderator i'm just somebody yeah
i feel like i see
all sides of people's different
perspectives and i'm able to like wait
here's what maybe you're not seeing
but like i'll get caught up in thinking
i'm that too much and try to solve
everybody's arguments on facebook yeah
i've done it for years but
it's like it's so easy to get caught up
on
facebook but um um
because uh don't go ahead uh freaking
i think black lives matter is deeper
than
just black lives matter it's like
it's basically like our signs said like
obviously all lives matter it's just
like it said
we know that all lives matter we're not
arguing with you that all lives don't
matter
but right now in this time of day black
lives are in danger and they matter
right now
and we need everybody to realize that
like i was kind of telling you earlier
uh i'm biracial like i grew up
not knowing if i was too black for the
white kids or too white for the black
kids
and um i was like even like
so when we did our we had a protest over
uh
by the monticello and there's like a
newspaper guy there
and he was just like so what do you
think about everything and stuff
and i was just like you know like i
think we
we make progress and stuff and then
something like george floyd happens and
and we're like right back at square one
and um freaking
um like
was i gonna say freaking we're right
back at square one
and uh like um
how should i put this
like it's a good thing we do have the
cameras and stuff now
because now we can actually see it and
it's kind of like uh
it was almost like watching like a real
life lynching
i feel like and this is like the first
time in history that we've seen
all 50 states like protesting which i
think is huge
and um you see a lot of white people out
there
of course and i think they woke up too
as in like they
after watching george floyd i think they
yeah even though like there's been like
a lot
over the past 10 years you could see but
like george zimmerman got to sell his
gun he killed trayvon with for a quarter
million dollars on ebay
you know so like um weird world
right very crazy world and so like
i think it's like i said earlier like
2020 has been messed up but i don't
think i'll go in vain
no because yeah i think it brought
everybody together like through the
hardest times
yeah i mean it's a time of healing like
our collective consciousness our our
whole society our
whole system like i think
that the blm movement is going to be
seen as like over the course of the next
few years
as like the the head the the point
of like this huge way bigger movement
like because that
so the way that quality like we're we're
changing in so many ways in in
i just think that we've evolved out of
just the way the constitution works i
think that we need a way more
complicated system
i think that we have i mean look like
look at what facebook is doing to us
like
we shouldn't be such suckers to like
things that we're addicted to like our
phones and stuff and it's turning us
all this [__] is turning us against each
other yeah we need in
and it's companies are selling it to us
like
companies are taking our attention and
selling it back to us companies are
getting us addicted to their platforms
they're we just are at this like huge
place in society where we're super
technologically advanced and we're
getting smart as [__]
like citizens are getting smarter and
smarter and we're figuring out more
stuff
but we don't really know how to handle
it we don't really know what to do with
it it's very confusing
like i think we just need a huge change
i
i don't i remember talking about
politics growing up
hardly ever dude like and now they're
all they all talk about politics
right there's cool shootings they're
crazy
yeah school shootings weren't around
like that no like those like dude and
look at depression rates and suicide
rates and
all these terrible mental health and
it's like it's real we're not what are
we doing about like
and and i mean i guess i think they try
to hide it for years i think they try to
like
because you can make money you can make
money if you're big pharma you know you
can make money off selling
selling antidepressants and selling all
these bills to to people
right sure and it covers up puts a
little band-aid instead of treating the
symptoms so we got to start treating the
symptoms we have everything
of racism kids are smart now
yeah dude we got to start acting like
you're smart let them be smart dude like
let them make some [__] decisions if
they're that smart you know
like we've got everybody who's in like
our political system like they're all 80
plus years old or something man like
and that's not that's not inherently
that doesn't actually just mean just
because i said they're old doesn't mean
that they're all incompetent that's not
true
no but i think we do need to realize
that they lived an entirely different
life than us and now we have this entire
generation who has
like a different view on reality yeah we
need to make some room for that new
reality
right here people protesting against us
they're all
60 or older yeah all of them what do you
i've had issues with my grandparents
dude and they i lived with my
grandparents growing up here and there
you know
so so what can we do
okay so what can we do so we have you
have your grandparents i know people in
my life like i've i've had a couple
conversations where i've
you know um since this since this has
started happening a lot of the racism
stuff
well when i started like you see all
views that's how i feel
yeah yeah yeah yeah so so where can we
take that
and offer advice to any listeners of
like where can you
in your own life like like how can you
help out on an individual level like
you know not like because i think that
that's what we could all do very well is
we can take a look at our own
interactions and see how we can change
our own interactions and if we have like
our grandparents and if there's any
chance we can maybe get a word with them
and say like
grandpa i'm like can i talk to you about
this because i think that you're wrong
and i i want
i want you to respect my opinion i know
that's like impossible like i'm not
saying
that's not the case match yeah
it didn't go great at all let me tell
them why um
i put desmond in a black lives matter
shirt that
me and him have matching ones and i made
him put his fist up
and i took a picture and i put it on
facebook trevor's grandma
that he lived with more than half his
life wrote on there and was like
he's a little boy how dare you put him
into that stuff he doesn't need to know
anything about that and like went
hard on me and i'm like hold up this is
my child and he's going to know what's
right from wrong
and i'm going to teach him that yeah
like
and then trevor garner history
and they know the right side of history
right they say they're not racist but
i feel like this will be in the history
books
like some point you know i'd like this
this will be in the history book
somewhere oh definitely all right and it
probably won't even book so probably on
like
an ipad you know it'll be floating
numbers in front of our faces it'll be
some
cool [__] virtual reality so when kids
are reading that
i think i just want to be on the right
side and
well so how can we
i just want to be able to try to have
the difficult conversations the
uncomfortable like what what is it with
in that situation like those people
across the street
and instead of just saying because in my
head it's like okay well they're
they're wrong and dumb okay but what are
they thinking like what
what what's going on like what what
could they hear that will make them
not say that like we're right versus
you're wrong but like what are they not
understanding like why can't we come
together
because because we live in a world we we
this thing that we have here in america
is literally like the freedom experiment
this is very difficult to work out we
have to have
people who are conservative and we have
to have people who are are
left like like you've got you we've got
it
well we've got to coincide is the thing
that that's this whole great thing that
makes america so great is that we have
those people we have
the healers who take care of the wounded
and they care about love
and then we have the ones we've always
had the warriors the people who take
care of our homes and they make sure we
have a fire
they fight enemies and there's we've
grown throughout
so many years to make our society the
way it is
and for it to like feel like it's
reversing right now it seems [__]
weird like what is going on like what um
they need to stop looking at the color
of skin yeah
like we're not a threat i get dark as
hell and i'm
everything well but so what's different
in my i mean okay like when i was
talking to my kyle
like i brought it up i was like bro this
feels awkward because like we've never
talked about this but it's like
it's because you know that typical like
i don't see color but it's like
i don't it's my boy it's like my buddy
so when your friend walks in you just
you don't that's not the first thing you
think of yeah and so
i mean i guess so it would be it would
be abnormal for really any situation to
like
all of a sudden think about all your
friends like backgrounds and their races
and like
uh like like hey what do you know about
your entire lineage can you tell me
about it because a lot of times we
connect on levels that aren't that we're
just
we connect as friends so like what's in
our heads that's
obvious that's not in other people's
heads i think
police brutality and like
my dad has went through it a lot but
like
sometimes i know it was his fault and
then sometimes i don't think it was his
fault
so like um
like what do you think about that like
well
like um like sometimes i know that he
brought up
himself yeah so but then i think
they're gonna get you but then i think
maybe they were just
after him because of the color of his
skin yeah i mean because he could be
treated differently
okay so when i watch when you watch say
like people interviewing trump on on a
podium
and everything that they say to him
there's like this feeling of resentment
there's this feeling of like
like he comes back at them with an
attitude i had this video
um that i was talking about uh is on my
youtube where i was talking about
i picked up a piece of trash it was a
coffee cup and the coffee cup
it was someone else's garbage and we
were just walking and i was like i can
grab that one piece of garbage and
that doesn't look all dirty and my house
is right here no big deal i picked it up
but the way that i was holding it was
like this like
two fingers i wasn't like it wasn't warm
you know like it's not mine
but if that was my coffee that i had
gotten from that same [__] store the
same coffee cup even in that morning
i'd hold it it's warm i'm drinking i put
it up to my mouth it's the same coffee
cup and i'm treating it i'm approaching
it
one's a piece of garbage because it's on
the side of the road and i have a as a
human i have a feeling towards it um and
i come
at it with some sort of difference than
it would be if it was mine
yeah and i think that what a lot of
people are doing without realizing it is
they're treating other people like a
piece of garbage in a warm
rather than warm water no seriously and
they don't realize that they're doing it
like they don't understand that they're
you're it's like approaching someone as
if they're about to say the dumbest
[__] thing you've ever heard it's
like no no
listen to every single person as a new
person and we
we we come at each other with this
resentment
it's you could cut it with a [__]
knife yeah like people just think they
know each other right away and they
think
they know everything you're about just
the way they look yeah i bet you if any
of those people instead of coming out
with their with their guns
if they parked on the same side and they
maybe even their introvert and they
pulled you to the side one person like
hey can you i don't understand this can
you
talk to me about it and said you know i
bet you any of you guys would be like
well let me tell you about my
experiences
yeah and you could [__] learn but we
come at each other as
enemies and we're not enemies though
like we're
like and i know that's like you know
it's it's racism is so much more
complicated that and it's so like deeply
embedded in our biology in certain ways
but we've seen it unwind people we've
seen we've seen people change the way
they think have you guys heard of i
think it's
uh uh daryl harold davis he was on joe
rogan and he like converted kkk members
yeah he's a black man dude you guys the
episode is
a black man who can converted a ton of
kkk members like he
he has like friends that they after they
had met and they like gave him their
robes of like hey i'm never wearing this
again you changed my life you changed my
behavior
so i'm just saying i know that it's
possible bro this is good you guys got
to check that out
i think it's daryl davis i could be
wrong but okay um
i think the simple thing is just like
getting back to like
how would you want someone to you how
you want to be treated kind of thing you
know
and um like we grew up in this town
longview kelso and
it's obviously mostly white but there's
like
still a lot of colors here in this town
you know mexicans blacks
puerto ricans asians whatever like and
um that's the cool thing about america
too though is that
we're one big melting pot so
you think from the 60s to the 80s
to the 20 20 the 20th century
to now like yeah we've made
a little no more like real slaves but
people can still look at their lives as
in this nine to five is a real [__] up
job like it could still feel like you're
a slave
in a way you know to the white man or
whatever the masa
freaking and i can still [__] with
people too a little bit you know in a
way
and so like um just get in the
just have people having new mindsets
would be the big thing
yeah shift in that mindset yeah which i
don't know how to do that yeah
i mean we're open-minded like we're you
know a lot of our of course young people
praying the next generation is more
open-minded
and stuff you know they seem smart they
seem really smart you know a
how do we set the stage for him you know
like yeah you know like i
like i will 10 years ago i was 15
and a lot of the same stuff was still
going on
you know and i pray desmond will be
almost 14 and 10 years you know like i
hope he's not
going through the same [__] yeah no way
there's no way i'll [__] my pants if
we're still going through racism
and what's crazy too is how much life
changes though
over like 20 years just 20 years 10 20
years how much should change from the
70s to the 90s
right that's so crazy to me so i'm
thinking about that
we're definitely evolving man like we're
at pace
yeah i mean look at like cancel culture
even like cancel culture is a good
example
like we're evolving but we like we're
doing it in kind of stupid-ass ways like
you can't pull up something that
somebody said like 2010
yeah like like if it was so long ago it
doesn't
like our reality like what was okay you
saw my old twitter different back then
you saw my old twitter in 2010 i would
definitely be canceled
bro i would i would literally 2010 on my
facebook and i came across it
within the last year and i didn't delete
it because i'm not someone who likes to
delete old [__]
[__] it's who i was yeah but like i
literally would tweet word or
on facebook even i would put out uh kid
cuddy
lyrics exactly i literally said the n
word on my own facebook yeah like
but because i would just copy and paste
the lyrics yeah now i know that's not
okay at all of course i wouldn't do that
yeah but like like man
like how cool am i supposed to know that
yeah like it's a different thing that's
what i'm saying is it's different it's
changed it's it's
developed into this weird thing like
these sites
and our society along with them have
changed and they've changed
who we are but now we can say like oh i
understand why that's not the right
that's not the best thing to do that's
not the best thing to put on my facebook
so now you don't you know right
but it's not people too soft and
sensitive though
i mean cancel culture yes because i
don't think we
should be policing our every single word
i think we should like when we have
areas where we're like okay i want to
make sure i'm not like incorrectly
saying these sort of things i want to
make sure that i'm not being an arrogant
prick about this
certain thing but other than that i
think that we shouldn't police our own
words i think that we should be able to
express ourselves freely yeah i think we
should be able to have difficult
conversations
yes i don't know how comedians still do
it
i think i see comedians as one of the
most important roles in our society
especially right now
if they weren't on stage saying like the
edgy [__] yeah we would not
we would be listening to [__] karen
every day and she'd say everything's
offensive and we gotta wait
like we've gotta be able to push our
edge like
that doesn't mean that anybody who gets
offended [__] you you're getting plowed
over
like it just means that
we've got to be able to always find our
edge and
and live at it because that's what makes
our whole culture and our whole society
so
oh you son of a [__] he just starts
being right there
let me just take him out really quickly
yes go ahead okay
that's funny blue
good old blue who got after it
what's up what's up still on the radio
the podcast see where the paw does
what is it called nothing
listen pain makes us write songs hope
makes
us sing them i love that i like that
i want to think of something cool to
write on the wall
you said we could he brought the markers
out i know but i don't know anything
cool
i was just going to keep it real or
don't keep it at all
oh that's always putting everybody's
yearbooks
you're funny say it again
keep it real or don't keep it at all
that's funny
that could be a tattoo no
no
he didn't even have that much opinion he
was just he didn't pee that much
just a little tingle
well we've been in it for a while i feel
like how long ago
my first ever podcast i was yeah
we got more than that too oh nice um
that wasn't the i'll tell you that's in
the joe button right and they do
what how long is your podcast usually
yours is very long yeah usually i mean
sometimes two and a half hours sometimes
hour 45.
i've done like 45 minute ones it's
really hard to gauge like a lot of times
i'm working on
their time and a lot of times which is
like a hard position to put myself in
because i don't know if i'm always
correct about it i'm
also trying to read the other person
like if i notice like oh okay they're
slowing down
they're not because this is something
that i've gotten good at because yeah
you can tell but bro like
talking for three hours is exhausting
yeah so a lot of people who don't do it
very often like i can
sense when my guest is like yeah bro i'm
not in my head
so i try to help him out you know oh no
i'm enjoying this is my first ever
podcast
i listened to joe but like i was saying
like he
does usually two and a half to three
hours every week
twice a week and then obviously rogan's
is live
so he can you never know what his is
gonna be right i've seen him do like a
four hour one
he just did a four one of post malone
whoa yeah it was dank
yeah i saw the first like 20 minutes of
that that was a good one
it was just a great like i love those
conversations like they ain't really
about
anything they're just they're just off
the wall yeah dude it's just like
using the human voice to like giggle and
laugh and explore little things and
stuff i have a question before we get
off hit me with it
what are your top five favorite artists
the top five favorite artists all right
yes
i wanna know okay all right so um
i don't know if i'm going to be able to
correctly order them that's okay
wait is it going to be hip-hop or
anything i say anything
let's go anything i feel like okay so
john bellian is definitely up there he's
one of my favorites he's a he's a pop
artist but he's
um he's kind of like versatile he does a
little bit of everything too right
yeah i mean he does everything like eric
bellinger sorry
yeah he's uh john billion yeah so he's
so him
um i don't listen to as much
anymore the last year but i have [__]
with russ i think russ is one of the
more talented rappers in the game
uh yeah joe button has a pull-up
interview with him i don't know if
you've seen that yes i did
yeah they've had well they've had two
like they had one back then when there
was beef and it was kind of like a
little
struggle yeah
i can literally put his cd in and listen
to every song
uh-huh yeah i got dude i wrote the wave
of he was posting a soundcloud
song it was like once a week that's the
greatest feeling bro and it was just
like every week he would just post a new
soundcloud so i'm like god this guy is
just [__] banging right here it's
like
a two-minute 16-second song it's just
solid and he does everything
yeah yeah and john billion does well he
works with other people now but he
got himself on by by doing everything
himself and that's like very inspiring
to me that's what like kind of my thing
is like i'm always trying to [__]
figure out how to do it all myself so
right
now we're going to sorry real quick
and we're freaking just random
spotify playlists and russ is what they
want
and willy wonka came on we're like this
guy's pretty good
yeah not even a year later he's just
blown up yeah dude yeah yeah it was it
was cool to see him
see him blow up i was definitely one of
those like hipsters i was like yeah bro
i was on him two years ago
right i know you all like him now i'm
the same he does the same
okay let me let me think of artists i
got a two so far
it's hard i feel like if i listen back
to this later i'm like you [__]
forgot so and soon
right it's hard this one is always like
a
it could be a revolving for anybody okay
wait can i hold off on my two while you
guys give your five
yeah and then like if i remember one
i'll just [__] rudely interrupt you
and just let me go insert it yeah go
ahead
okay so um eminem
of course uh tupac
uh p diddy lauren
lauren hill and uh
it's a mix between kendrick lamar and
missy elliott
you know that's not a matchup i would
think would be at the end but i feel it
dude and those are my hardcore like i
could go i can listen to them
every day all day this is yes
she just came out with her is it good
yeah
yeah it's with lizzo okay okay i like
that it's a good match-up nice
okay she don't get her flowers i got hov
biggie kendrick wale and then this
fifth can always be like andre
kanye i don't i don't mess with kanye
yeah
it could be
[Music]
a pog it could be anybody you know
wu-tang anyway from the wu
like you know like the fifth one i feel
like can always it just
trade it always someone it's always
someone different i feel that
yeah it's like a five and a five and a
half yeah my top four for sure is hov
biggie kendrick and wales yeah okay
all right all right i gotta try to think
of my other three
um i mean when you said kanye i have
always honestly been a kanye fan
um lately it's been rough but yeah
he's just oh my god bro trevor has his
lyrics tattooed what do you got what is
it
everything i'm not made me everything i
am i love it from graduation
hell yes oh yeah dj premiered the beat
um i think i think kid cuddy is in the
top five for me i think that's
that's a good one for you this is a big
part of our generation yeah
um and then man i feel like i'm just
gonna insert them
but i have one guy his name's um dylan
owen and he inspires me so much so he's
basically like
he kind of writes like poetry in a sense
it's it's musical poetry
yeah um it's it's hard to explain it's
like
because it's also hip-hop uh but he's
east coast and he's just like very raw
and he's uh he's just like a just a
skinny white dude just speaking from his
heart
but he's just like the way he does it is
very original i really like
people who are doing things only the way
that they're doing it just like i'm like
[__] i'm just so drawn to it can't
forget mac miller oh
man i love mac miller he'll be in my
head
we were talking about uh with mac miller
he was one of the first artists
that i felt like i was young and i got
twitter around when he was getting
poppin and i felt like he was like
you grew up on the internet no literally
when he died i felt weird like i
was super sad literally i was like one
of the first like
like people who had famous people who
had died that i was like damn bro like i
feel like that's like my friend
yeah that one hurt for sure um
i thought i went to two years i went to
two concerts like yeah
i never saw him live oh we did yeah
we're about to go to swimming's tour
like i'm super good he's getting he's
tapping into like his
true potential i feel like he was just
now getting in there like
i mean like musically so many like
great artists are like they're just
getting better and better like
imagine mack like if he hadn't passed
imagine him in 20 years like what kind
of makeup
legend is a legend of mine oh yeah he is
yeah
but he um i don't know
like justin lapham showed him to me
mm-hmm jaleb was super on him yeah yeah
oh yeah
was rapping a little bit back yeah did
you just go to jenna's house and like
pick beats for him and try to like do
wrap up nice
freaking um mac though i feel like he
came from like the
2010 era he did where like it was like
coal kendrick
was up there for sure yeah logic like
those guys were all like in a little
class together yeah
and mac was like since he was the white
guy he was always like kind of like
he could have joined tde you know like
people don't know that kind of stuff
like
he he was really cool with like
all those guys like um
even schoolboy were actually like best
friends they were like musically he was
literally typing like his last two
albums were like
real like he was singing and playing
instruments and like when i went to good
am tour he was playing instruments
and yeah it was like turning into like
it wasn't just like a beat off
wherever right yeah he was really
connecting i love seeing an
artist grow into that like i was talking
about with jonathan yeah like he like he
he taught himself like he did go to
music school and he had like his own
talents before because he just like
[__] always did it he sung and he rap
and he just kept working on it
but then like as his albums progressed
and he got like more money and he was
able to do the things like
he got more connections you know like
now his most recent album
is not so much him making beats but he's
literally able to hire like full choirs
and [__] because he wants to make that's
the music in his head you know yeah
so like just seeing artists progress and
then be able to have like
four people yes john billy writes four
people so he wrote um like the hook for
rihanna and eminem monster under your
bed um
i'm friends with the party next door
yeah he does he writes a bunch for
rihanna i love party next door too yeah
yeah yeah
he he writes a bunch for beyonce i bet
belly ham does too
yeah yeah well okay so so so bellian did
he had one that was like sent to beyonce
he has a lyric about it i forget exactly
what it was but it was like
supposed to go to beyonce but he missed
the call so they sent it to christina
aguilera or something he has a line
about it
but it's like it's cool man he's always
like mentioning like
and i think and you probably shouldn't
he has a couple lines
in his earlier [__] where i think that
he wrote on some [__]
that he's not allowed to say that he
wrote on like right off on it
yeah dude there was there was a couple
of lines that he that he mentioned that
i've always
been like hmm did you write that thing
in that kanye song and he's not allowed
you sign a [__] nda or something well
kanye has been pretty
upfront that he has writers for him yeah
i mean connie is just the creative mind
like i feel like that dude is just like
give him something to where he can work
on it and he'll he'll put something on
he'll sprinkle something on it close and
i think he means well there's a thing
about kanye i think he means well and i
think he
he's wait he's not obviously not like
called dropout late registration kanye
anymore which is fine because he's like
one of a million grammys and like if you
want to call illuminati the kardashians
are like in the illuminati for sure
so like you know he's in that world and
he's in like
like he's friends with trump and stuff
you know like he's just like with all
these like
republican conservative people you know
so he's like talks a certain way now
and uh i don't think like we lost him
but then again then you see him at like
a rally or something you know
like giving money to black lives matter
so it's kind of confusing like
i feel like he's just one big um
contradiction walking contradiction in a
way
yeah it's very confusing it's very hard
to understand what the [__] he's doing
with the vest on yeah so okay so
it's pissing me out bro because it's
hard because the damn
the media damn it but like so i had i
saw that
where he was talking about like was like
harriet tubman or something like he's
talking about he's
saying some weird [__] like an abortion
yeah but bro
but okay and then i saw like a longer
like eight minute clip of it or whatever
it was
and if you show with the other stuff
that he was talking about it all came
full circle kind of
yeah but like the just that clip of him
talking about that random [__] that
they put out they're like
he goes off on this and it was right in
the middle of like people being enraged
about certain things
and so like i saw it and as a person who
is
biased towards kanye like i wanted to be
on his side
but once i saw that i was like dude what
the hell like i i was pissed at kanye
for a second and now i think that i
understand kind of what he was talking
about when he's it's his delivery
yeah i mean he's a crazy ass though and
but i said i think that i'm someone who
understands what he's actually saying i
don't i can't
be a genius you have to be crazy bro
like i believe in that
dude i think you really do have to be
like crazy in some way to be a genius
dude i i think so too yeah
like that's dude that's been like this
whole thing last couple years for me is
i'm just like
i just [__] cut my tether man i'm
like i'm not afraid to be the crazy guy
anymore like i want to be the crazy guy
i heard you're talking about certain
things on your podcast i was like oh he
don't care anymore [__]
like that that's what always held me
back was uh
i was actually kind of embarrassed to
even talk about everything i did talk
about
today but of course man of course dude
but it's so
empowering and so powerful that you
talked about that seriously thank you
someone can maybe relate you know
somebody definitely can yeah
we have like i was saying man we have
all these things that we all
really really go through and
just because they're not like societally
okay they're not acceptable we don't
know how to process them we don't have
to go through them
we don't know how to like not feel
ashamed about ourselves about them or
not
they like [__] us because we have
nobody to talk to about it sometimes
like
it's dude you're kind of like just given
a life and then once you get older
you're like oh okay now i gotta grab the
reins you know like
a lot of times we're just kind of a ball
of habits just kind of following what we
were taught and we don't really realize
we have much control
are you trying to just find someone that
you can relate with online
that's another thing what online maybe
is good for
is just trying to find someone that you
can relate with you know in a way or
some
community man i think i think you're the
community podcast
yeah that's cool yeah it's cool you said
that
because i because i try to keep it open
for like i have a lot of people
in our community but i try to always
like remember i do have other listeners
throughout
yeah but so i'm always trying to like
explain our situation it's funny when
you talk about like we're like
yeah so it's probably weird to you but
we have 500 percent raised in the woods
you know like it's just such a cool
peculiar world that we have but i think
um you know with the internet and
everything going on right now
and um like you sharing sharing your
personal story you sharing your personal
story like
it rebuilds from the inside out that
word community
community really is like like we can
connect with one another
based off of starting out our interests
you know we can connect those bridges
and then we can find people who are just
like us or people who
have had similar experiences with us and
then it makes us feel less alone in
places where we didn't even realize we
felt alone
yeah you know and and i think that when
people can and
get on public airwaves and just say like
hey here's some [__] that happened to me
and i'm doing pretty good now and i'm
[__] plugging through it
[Music]
it's up to you babe okay it's kind of a
lot
what you can tell it if you want to let
me tell you okay okay it's all on you
i don't want her to hear you though your
mom doesn't have spotify
okay um so
i feel for kids that um
are like super close with their moms but
like
are like more like friends with them you
know yeah like i used
i did a lot of bad stuff too with my mom
but like
um she tried to kill herself one time
she like slit her wrists and was like
bleeding out on
in the street and i had to go to the
hospital with her
and we're like in this weird room
where like all the crazy people go and
she was literally just
wrapped up dude like they had it like
tied up and stuff like in a
crazy suit you know yeah and they they
weren't even they didn't even clean her
up or anything
and uh like i think that
really changed her too like she feels
bad about that all the time
but um because you guys are more best
friends
than mother and son yeah it's like a
weird relationship
so like seeing that like i just
just want people to know like if someone
is going through something like that
it's like not your fault like i felt
like i was like why would she want to do
that to me you know
and stuff right yeah yeah um you took
that guilt that was not yours
yeah and like so she just
like always like apologizes for it and
stuff
but just not like it's not your fault
right she had her own demons going on
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
we heal from stuff like that i mean i i
i'm
i'm optimistic about a future where
our entire mental mental health system
is just handled differently
um yeah i everything is so weird when it
comes to it we don't really know how to
talk about it it's almost like a taboo
thing
i don't think we handle it correctly i
don't think we understand our minds as
much as we think we do
yeah um and do we put too much in that
kind of energy in the world maybe
what do you like talking about it or do
you think it i think we need to
i think that we need to because i think
that it's the reality that's facing a
lot of us i mean like me with my mental
health i was like
quietly depressed for many [__] years
because
i mean a lot of us knew that yeah but
because i
didn't feel comfortable talking about it
because i had my i need to make sure my
armor is safe i need to make sure my ego
is tough i need to make sure that
the world knows i'm good i need to make
sure everybody else is taken care of you
all look weak
yeah don't want to look weak like all
these things that like society
inherently inevitably without us really
knowing puts on us
you know it's we're dealing with the
replica repercussions of them now so
i appreciate you you sharing that too i
don't think jazz was ever
like she's always upbeat and having like
jazz is a huge thing because i have my
moments but yeah
she's i i guess i handle it different
yeah like i like a good cry you know
yeah dude yeah i don't get it
or any movie i'm with you see like and
that helps me get my emotion out i'll be
like
put on that movie that makes me cry and
i just need to let it all out yeah
dude sometimes you're you'll notice
you're just at the edge
of crying and you're like oh shoot maybe
i needed to get this guy you need to get
it out
so good i'll watch parks and rec for
like the third time and it's just like
not even think significant but i just
know what's about to happen so i start
crying
this has been therapeutic for you yeah
dude this has been yeah
yeah definitely like just being able to
talk with people about it and um
openly like it's funny because a lot of
times people's minds
yeah like like you don't realize like
i'll listen back to myself on the
podcast and i'm like [__] bro i guess
i'm more confident about that [__] than
i thought i was like i just came out and
said it right
but yeah but it's you know like trying
to live it out and trying to just
express myself i think that
you know i dude i gained so much from
podcasts myself like i was telling you
like i when i first started listening to
podcasts i'm getting better
yeah dude it's made me it's made me more
of an intellectual i feel like it's
it's sharpened my my vocabulary almost
definitely yeah i mean and it's
it it kind of points out how weird
conversation is like we actually don't
have a lot of super extended
conversations like maybe with our loved
ones like if you two at home
yeah we're always available so uh i
think having the podcast man like i was
just i started watching
just on youtube i was saying i'd watch
like joe rogan clips there's like 60
minutes long it'd be like cool like you
know they give you a little summary i'm
like oh
so-and-so talks about meditation cool
and then i would go like
oh that guest scene is pretty cool i
should watch the whole episode and then
i'll watch the episodes and then i'll go
read that guest book and it just led me
into these [__] just so like it's
just that and that's what my last couple
years have been it's just like this
healing of following like
my interests and following like
following my bliss as i like to say yes
like
in in it and i think
pushing anybody towards their bliss
pushing anybody towards just
learning like honestly i know a lot a
lot of people aren't into podcasts but i
think that a lot of people who are
have had some sort of like communication
like yeah yeah like start changing the
way they think and stuff yeah
like and i've tried to find some for her
i just i haven't really gotten into
anything i listen all yours
i don't but i don't listen to anything
else there's nothing wrong with that i
mean
there's there's so many different kinds
but maybe it's because i know
you and everyone that's on your thing so
i'm like yeah
connections yeah yours is the most
oh i don't listen to any others nice
i don't have any podcasts well a lot of
girls listen to like
uh how to conveniently murder their
husband and those sort of things
a lot of those murder mysteries swag
girls are always listening
thrillers oh no scared no scare i get
nightmares
dude there's uh okay there is one good
one i could recommend you
um i'll get the official name from
shaylee but you may even like it but
it's uh
it was on the it's like an opioid crisis
one it was on spotify and it was
it was about fentanyl like about like
this this reporter did like
all the and they interviewed like
someone who has been in jail and he's
from portland
like it was so interesting like seeing
like
people they they met with like people
from the black market over in china
and like this was like that might
is like the underground world of
fentanyl is what it was i'll get the
name but
okay but anyway there's what i'm saying
is
you know podcasts and you know these
longer form things
are it's a lot like tv shows it's a lot
like you know it's
it's entertainment but it's a better
radio station yeah yeah it's it's a
little more controlled it's not so much
like you're kind of fed things that you
didn't want to get fed i don't
surface stuff yeah it's some real [__]
most
if you if you find the right ones yeah
well and hey i think at this time in our
life in a society
it's they're [__] important we have
long conversations we have people who
like you're talking about joe budden
like
man like he used to be beef all day you
know he's like intelligent and
he's always been intelligent of course
but but like yeah they talk about real
[__] and
other people open up about real [__]
relationships like
everything podcasts are they're a cool
thing that are happening
and it's crazy just how many there is
now though
yeah it's crazy like i remember five
years ago like it was
not like this yeah everybody's starting
one now
which is a good thing it could be more
people talking yeah yeah
more money and in your own lane too like
like do your thing like dude there's
people who like
[__] the the red nascar fans
you know like like they just like like
the the blue
smurf t-shirt lovers podcast episode one
like
whoever wants like you just the thing
that you're into damn i should see if
there's any photography ones oh i
guarantee there's tons of photography
ones for sure
dude no doubt yeah yeah there's so many
and there's so many and that because
that's the thing because like look at me
like like what are you gonna look for
like a dj who kind of likes meditation
he's learning about mindfulness
mental health like i don't know no you
know how do you look better
yeah you just you just stumble into your
interests yeah so
that is dope you're on spotify now
though and everything yeah
does do you just since you got premium
you can just
oh yeah yeah no it's super i'm on
spotify and apple music and all those
uh australians amazon just came out with
their they're releasing their own
podcast platform i got an email about
that yesterday so i gotta submit myself
uh soundcloud is the one that i'm not on
because you have to pay for
pay for a premium membership and i have
[__] beef with soundcloud because my
dj mixes back in the day and i'm just
i remember these i remember i mean i
used to listen to those yeah
i got them but they're all my mixed
cloud um no soundcloud anymore
um but but but on mixed cloud but no so
i'm on a bunch of different platforms
with so essentially what i do is i
submit it to one
um you basically have like one uploading
service
and so i type out all my episode i get
all the thumbnail i put up the audio
clip it like helps me organize it like
what episode number is this and all that
and then once i push it on there then
they handle it and they send it out to
the other
so it's like within within like 15
minutes usually i'll see it on spotify
within an hour i'll see on apple music
then it'll be on google play
you know it floats after a couple years
see if someone from different countries
or states
listen to your stuff yeah yeah i've got
a shitload of people from other
countries
okay not a shitloader i'm exaggerating
but
like it shows me the stats and it'll be
like you know it'll be like
three or four people from [__] new
zealand or a couple people from like uh
like
czech republic or that's you know a
couple sprinkles
yeah yeah and it's it's cool because i
feel like a lot of
a lot of people come back to my podcast
like they don't just listen to one like
they find another one
and because it's i don't want it to be
something where
you can't tune into just one like if
somebody doesn't listen to the podcast
if they just want to listen to one
episode they would still enjoy it it's
not like yeah they're going to feel like
left out so i want to treat like you
know there's a there's room for a new
listener and every
variety of 50 something now yeah i got
50 posted so far
yeah i've got a couple cool ones coming
out too i've got a
i just interviewed these guys um who
have they have another podcast
it was just cool like i had this
intuition to message them on um
on reddit because they posted like hey
we're looking to be featured on
anybody's podcast here's what we do
and i was like [__] these guys seem cool
yeah so uh they're called camp
re-education
and what they do is they basically like
test their biases like they're from
chicago new york and they're
they're like we want to relearn what we
learned like we want to
dive deep into a subject for two weeks
and completely immerse ourselves into it
so they actually did one uh recently on
reality tv they're like we know nothing
about reality tv we think it's dorky we
think it's what like they had their bias
against it
and then they dove into it for two weeks
and they came out and they're like we
know
we there's it's a whole world that we
didn't know about we know this about it
now they did the same thing on like
micro dosing
they're gonna do it on like demon
summoning or something like
super interesting guys but yeah so i i
had a podcast episode with them just
like kind of talking about that's gonna
be cool
yeah so is that the is that the only one
you've ever like the one besides this
have you done
have you done any more besides that are
like ready to
ready to post no no like have you done
any other people's podcasts
oh um i'm on next week i'm on
maybe this week next week i think i'm on
one podcast which is
a movie review podcast over in florida
and
these dudes that i met i made their
intro actually um for their podcast
and they uh they like just do movie
reviews and they're called the box
office bingers and
they'll do like if there's a new series
that comes out on netflix they'll binge
it
and they'll do like a full-on like i
love your movies yeah dude
yeah i love you guys
[Laughter]
i missed seeing you guys when i would
just go smoke a big old j out in the
parking lot at 10 p.m
yeah yeah i love i love going to the
route i sincerely miss the movie theater
we might open oh [__] the only thing so
many people can come
25 25 would you do like
still do like late movies and stuff do
you think um so they would like spread
it out like
um not one every hour it'd be like
spread it out
and there'd be a late one of course but
no hot food only popcorn and
candy and like nachos but nothing that
we have to make yeah simplify for you
and then uh we'll have to clean every
sea
after every movie rough which is okay
yeah but i mean hey it's something yeah
i i think the world probably needs that
little bit of sanity right i think
we need the movies we got to get out of
the house a little bit
do something honestly just having like
and i know there's no fans but just
watching there's basketballs back now
i know and it's so weird like watching
it because there's no fans or anything
but
you still need to watch it's still nice
just have you gotten used to it like how
is it no fans
oh man they literally try to put up like
people watching it from like their
phones and laptops
their faces on like these walls
they're just trying so weird it was so
creepy oh yeah i don't know that they
should just avoid that
and they had like fake like applause or
like defense
i yeah i heard about that too like dude
this is
weird but i mean we'll get players are
still kind of neat the players are still
playing great
but just like holy crap it's like an
open gym
and it's just like when there's an
atmosphere there dude the pressure's on
you know right bro
you know vibe is everything yeah and
like that that's that energy that you
feel when you're a player when people
are feeling off the crowd
yeah imagine football with no crowd that
would be a weirdest thing ever
what if there is this on my way here
they canceled college football already
they canceled college so what do you
guys think about nfl i think you can
cancel that i don't know what they're
gonna do about the nfl
i'll cry but um yeah weird it is nice
though to
just watch something and get your mind
off everything for a minute
yeah you know like i watch the blazers
so like
just watching them for like when they
play just nice for
just besides seeing a bunch of [__]
online
right yeah dude you got to police how
much you're on the social media so
you're going to end up like jasmine in
his six hour long fight
it's so easy i'm never doing it again i
just did that one time
we'll end it on a good note did you guys
hear that the seattle kraken
the hockey team that's pretty cool i
mean i'm not i'm not like a huge hockey
fan but so
they announced a the release video was
where it was super tight too
but uh seattle is going to have their
own hockey alcohol right
huh yeah there's an alcohol cracker i've
i've been to a hockey game
yeah was it winter hawks yeah isn't it
fun is that it's so fun i love it yeah
yeah and i was
under 21. so i'd like to go now that oh
yeah you can have a beer too
heck yeah i'm really into soccer i
haven't been to a soccer game
i got into soccer in like 2014 and so i
went
it was the world cup you know like
happens every four years yeah yeah yeah
and
um usa did like pretty good in that it
was in brazil
and um after that i got into it so i
went to like a sounders game
in seattle and dude i was like right on
the field yeah
it was really cool like they're a lot
more physical than you think
yeah and um they're fastest but hockey
that should be dope i've played some
hockey video games
um they're really physical and losing
teeth and [__]
yeah yeah dude yeah it's a different
sport it's cool it's like
i feel like before i had really watched
it live i didn't understand it i was
like why would they fight it just seems
like this egotistical
like i'm too cool for it or something
but then i watched it and i'm like oh
this is just
it's that how they do things it's just
their sport like it's just
like like they have this like
cool camaraderie of like oh you [__]
with her goalie
yeah okay
like you could see little things happen
and you're like oh okay like
your boys are now on their side like
you're screwed you know or like if
there's someone like if it's uneven like
there's someone in the in the
timeout or whatever you're like okay now
they're getting their revenge
yeah then they start hitting their
sticks on the glass
get all amped up well it's going to be
weird without crowds but
um i mean it is better than nothing like
whatever sports we are going to get
you know and i'm hoping that i know like
it sucks to say terms like new normal
that sounds [__] gross in my mouth
but
like we really are gonna find a new
normal yeah and you know i think that
things are pretty crazy right now and i
think that things
there's days of really havoc but i think
i'm optimistic about the future i think
that this is all leading to something
beautiful and good i hope i will not go
in vain
yeah and then go we'll come back to it
and be like we needed that
yeah yeah i think we need to all just
slow down
check ourselves wake up call smack in
the mouth and
i do think after the pandemic that we
should still wear
masks and hopefully you wash your hands
i think you master around for i think
they'll be around
that's what yeah years ago ten years ago
you well
i don't know five ten years ago i don't
really know i wasn't there but uh you
if you walked into like a grocery store
grocery store
without a mask it'd be kind of rude
actually even before you're endemic
that's how they got their mindset set
yeah so i think it's a good thing
honestly maybe people won't get as sick
as much you know
yeah yeah we got to do something we got
to learn well both of you i appreciate
you both for coming
i'm glad that you're both coming out
thank you this is awesome dude
i'm glad we have to do it together yeah
dude that works perfectly yeah i don't
know like how to end
here's how we end listener take care of
yourselves
have a good day jasmine where can we
find your photography uh jasmine jean
visions on
all social media wonderful check her out
listeners take care of yourself love
yourself peace peace out
you